A Week Away is a drama, music, romance film directed by Roman White.
Troubled teen Will Hawkins has a run-in with the law that puts him at an important
crossroad: go to juvenile detention or attend a Christian summer camp.
At first a fish-out-of-water, Will opens his heart, discovers love with a camp
regular, and sense of belonging in the last place he expected to find it.
Avery, played by Bailee Madison.
Will Hawkins, played by Kevin G. Quinn.
Kristin, played by Sherri Shepherd.
David, played by David Koechner.
George, played by Jahbril Cook.
Presley, played by Kat Conner Sterling.
A Week Away is a 2021 American Christian musical
romance film directed by Roman White.
The film was written by Alan Powell, Kali Bailey, and Gabe Vasquez.
The film's songs were produced and mixed by Adam Watts and co-produced by Cory
Clark (the team also co-wrote the film's original songs with Powell).
The film stars Bailee Madison, Kevin Quinn, David Koechner, and Sherri
Shepherd with cameos from Amy Grant and Steven Curtis Chapman.
Producers for the film are Alan Powell, Gabe Vasquez, and Steve Barnett.
The film premiered on March 26, 2021, on Netflix.
The film introduces songs of Christian artists such as Michael W.
Smith, Amy Grant, and Steven Curtis Chapman to a younger generation with modern renditions of
songs like "The Great Adventure", "Dive", "Baby, Baby", and "Place in This World."
The film explores themes of summer camp, forgiveness,
musical, teen movie, teenage girl.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.